tamilqueens.com 2016-03-14

# Privacy Policy - Tamil actress photos-pictures & images of Tamil actors-TamilQueens

**The privacy of our visitors to TamilQueens.com is important to us.**

At TamilQueens **.** com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit Tamilqueens.com, and how we safeguard your information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.

## Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include  your name, postal addresses, email addresses, IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Ripe NCC), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

**Tamilqueens.com**  does not use cookies.

We also use third party advertisements like Google AdSense program(www.google.com/adsense) on **  our website** to support our costs.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed (Such as Google through the Google AdSense program. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to  **www.tamilqueens.com**  and other sites on the Internet. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited or to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.TamilQueens **.** com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers like Google AdSense program.You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.Tamilqueens **.** com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the [ads preference manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/) or [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> or <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> )

## Third Party Tracking Technology

This website uses a tracking technology called Google Analytics to obtain Site usage information  such as users Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, Internet domain and host names, browser  software, and the date and time that the website is visited, will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Data obtained through Google Analytics  does not include and is not linked to any personal information. Data from Google Analytics  allows us to monitor the use of this Site, understand how users find our website, and improve the  Site’s function and content.

Site usage data collected through Google Analytics is not shared with other Google products and  tools. Our use of Google Analytics is in compliance with Google’s Terms of Service. Google provides more information about [Google’s  privacy practices and information on how to opt-out of Google Analytics tracking](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html) of your web  browsing.

## Email Newsletter

This website operates an email newsletter program, used to inform subscribers about products and services supplied by this website. Users can subscribe through an online automated process should they wish to do so but do so at their own discretion. Some subscriptions may be manually processed through prior written agreement with the user.

Subscriptions are taken in compliance with international spam laws. All personal details relating to subscriptions are held securely and no personal details are passed on to third parties nor shared with companies / people outside of the company that operates this website.  Email marketing campaigns published by this website or it’s owners may contain tracking facilities within the actual email. Subscriber activity is tracked and stored in a database for future analysis and evaluation. Such tracked activity may include; the opening of emails, forwarding of emails, the clicking of links within the email content, times, dates and frequency of activity [this is by no far a comprehensive list]. This information is used to refine future email campaigns and supply the user with more relevant content based around their activity.

Subscribers are given the opportunity to un-subscribe at any time through an automated system. This process is detailed at the footer of each email campaign.

## Social Media Platforms

Communication, engagement and actions taken through external social media platforms that this website and it’s owners participate on are custom to the terms and conditions as well as the privacy policies held with each social media platform respectively.

Users are advised to use social media platforms wisely and communicate / engage upon them with due care and caution in regard to their own privacy and personal details. This website nor it’s owners will ever ask for personal or sensitive information through social media platforms and encourage users wishing to discuss sensitive details to contact them through primary communication channels such as by telephone or email.

This website may use social sharing buttons which help share web content directly from web pages to the social media platform in question. Users are advised before using such social sharing buttons that they do so at their own discretion and note that the social media platform may track and save your request to share a web page respectively through your social media platform account.

## Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

## Links to Other Websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Privacy Contact Information

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

**By E-mail:  tamilqueensinfo@gmail.com**

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
